ggmania.com 2005-12-10

# Privacy Statement

##  Privacy Statement for BOX Network ltd.

**BOX Network** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this network of websites: [ www.boxnetwork.net](http://www.boxnetwork.net/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used in creating a logging system which counts unique hits. __

####  Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. We do not use cookies in other parts of our Web site or as information for ourselves.

####  Personal Information 

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **BOX Network ltd.** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

####  Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

### Third Party Advertising 

We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here: [www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php)

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

webmaster@boxnetwork.net
